[
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0037",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 1,
    "question": "What is this popular landmark beside the Thames?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Kolner Dom",
    "Wronganswer2": "Babylon",
    "Wronganswer3": "Angkor Wat",
    "CORRECT": "London Eye",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0016",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "Which city has a hotel with a replica of the Eiffel Tower?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York",
    "Wronganswer2": "Shanghai",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tokyo",
    "CORRECT": "Las Vegas",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0010",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "Which natural landscape is at the border of Canada and the United states?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Dead Sea",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Great Barrier Reef",
    "Wronganswer3": "Easter Island",
    "CORRECT": "Niagra Falls",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0056",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 4,
    "question": "Which place does the President of Russia work and live?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Buckingham Palace",
    "Wronganswer2": "Elysee Palace",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Great Palace",
    "CORRECT": "Kremlin",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0098",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "How long is the Great Barrier Reef?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Less than 100 miles",
    "Wronganswer2": "Around 500 miles",
    "Wronganswer3": "Around 800 miles",
    "CORRECT": "More than 1,600 miles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0038",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "What is this observation tower built in Seattle for the World Expo in 1962?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Eiffel Tower",
    "Wronganswer2": "Notre Dame",
    "Wronganswer3": "White Tower",
    "CORRECT": "Space Needle",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0068",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 7,
    "question": "What is this cross-sea bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Tower Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Charles Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Rialto Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0054",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 8,
    "question": "What is this attraction of more than 13,000 miles long?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Yellowstone National Park",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hollywood",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ayers Rock",
    "CORRECT": "Great Wall of China",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0002",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 9,
    "question": "In which place can you meet Mickey Mouse and his friends?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Louvre",
    "Wronganswer2": "The White House",
    "Wronganswer3": "Times Square",
    "CORRECT": "Disneyland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0085",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 10,
    "question": "In which country would you find the Taj Mahal?",
    "Wronganswer1": "China",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pakistan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Kuwait",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0032",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 11,
    "question": "What is this One of the world's most famous Gothic buildings?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Space Needle",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sydney Opera House",
    "Wronganswer3": "Westminster Abbey",
    "CORRECT": "Big Ben",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0101",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 12,
    "question": "A statue of whom stands atop a hill in Rio de Janeiro?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Helios",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bartholdi",
    "Wronganswer3": "George Washington",
    "CORRECT": "Jesus Christ",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0049",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 13,
    "question": "What is this ancient Egyptian mausoleum building?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Louvre",
    "Wronganswer2": "Taj Mahal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Eiffel Tower",
    "CORRECT": "Great Sphinx",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0067",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 14,
    "question": "Where did Walt Disney open the first Disneyland Resort in 1955?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hong Kong",
    "Wronganswer2": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer3": "Orlando",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0057",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 15,
    "question": "What is the famous clock tower in London, England called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "London Eye",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Colosseum",
    "Wronganswer3": "Leaning Tower of Pisa",
    "CORRECT": "Big Ben",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0081",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 16,
    "question": "What is the Great Sphinx is made up of?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cement",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sands",
    "Wronganswer3": "Wood",
    "CORRECT": "Limestone",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0052",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 17,
    "question": "What is this Arizona attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Niagara Falls",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hyde Park",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Mediterranean",
    "CORRECT": "The Grand Canyon",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0094",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 18,
    "question": "Which landmark in Italy is a historical witness to the flourishing commercial capital of Renaissance?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Aswan High Dam",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pattaya Beach",
    "Wronganswer3": "Babylon",
    "CORRECT": "Historic Centre of Florence",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0022",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 19,
    "question": "Where did Islam originate?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cario",
    "Wronganswer2": "Baghdad",
    "Wronganswer3": "Kabul",
    "CORRECT": "Mecca",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0008",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 20,
    "question": "What is this one of the Seven Wonders?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Hanging Gardens of Babylon",
    "Wronganswer2": "Machu Picchu",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Colossus of Rhodes",
    "CORRECT": "Pyramids of Giza",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0030",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 21,
    "question": "What New York bridge was the last work designed by John Roebling, completed in the late 19th century?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Bridge Tower",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Belt Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Chapel Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "The Brooklyn Bridge",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0034",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "What is this Italian attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Duomo di Milano",
    "Wronganswer2": "Piazza San Marco",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pantheon",
    "CORRECT": "Leaning Tower of Pisa",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0009",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 23,
    "question": "Which major river flows across Cairo?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Niger",
    "Wronganswer2": "Yangtze",
    "Wronganswer3": "Amazon",
    "CORRECT": "Nile",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0020",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 24,
    "question": "Where can you visit Space Needle?",
    "Wronganswer1": "St. Paul, MN",
    "Wronganswer2": "Salem, OR",
    "Wronganswer3": "Denver,CO",
    "CORRECT": "Seattle, WA",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0031",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 25,
    "question": "What mountain range connect to the northern border of Italy?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Fuji",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Rocky",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Himalayas",
    "CORRECT": "The Alps",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0053",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 26,
    "question": "What is this most outstanding ancient architectural complex in Greece?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Angkor Wat",
    "Wronganswer2": "Notre Dame de Paris",
    "Wronganswer3": "Buckingham Palace",
    "CORRECT": "Acropolis",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0086",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 27,
    "question": "Which landmark was caused by Colorado river's flowing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Cook",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Barrier Reef",
    "Wronganswer3": "Fujiyama",
    "CORRECT": "The Grand Canyon",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0007",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 28,
    "question": "Which mountain range's main part locates in China?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Southern Alps",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bismarck",
    "Wronganswer3": "Queen Maud",
    "CORRECT": "Himalayan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0006",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 29,
    "question": "Which President's face is NOT on Mount Rushmore?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "Wronganswer2": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "Wronganswer3": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "CORRECT": "Harry S. Truman",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0045",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "What is this stately English building?",
    "Wronganswer1": "London Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Big Ben",
    "Wronganswer3": "London Eye",
    "CORRECT": "Westminster Abbey",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0019",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 31,
    "question": "Where is the Statue of Liberty?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ankara",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sacramento",
    "Wronganswer3": "Phoenix",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0080",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 32,
    "question": "Why did Shi Huandi ordered to build the Great Wall?",
    "Wronganswer1": "To Defend Aliens",
    "Wronganswer2": "To Climb The Mountains",
    "Wronganswer3": "To Go Hiking",
    "CORRECT": "To Keep Enemies Out",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0079",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 33,
    "question": "Where is the Hotel Hershey located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Nevada",
    "Wronganswer2": "Vermont",
    "Wronganswer3": "North Dakota",
    "CORRECT": "Pennsylvania",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0047",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 34,
    "question": "What is this cathedral sitting on the Seine River in Paris?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Borobudur",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mosque of St",
    "Wronganswer3": "Taj Mahal",
    "CORRECT": "Notre Dame",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0089",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "Which is an iconic building in St. Louis?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Empire State Building",
    "Wronganswer2": "Central Park",
    "Wronganswer3": "MGM Grand",
    "CORRECT": "Gateway Arch",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0070",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 36,
    "question": "What is this stone bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Great Belt Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Chapel Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Brooklyn Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Rialto Bridge",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0028",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "What is this landmark in Rome?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mogao Grottoes",
    "Wronganswer2": "Notre Dame",
    "Wronganswer3": "Arch Of Triumph",
    "CORRECT": "The Colosseum",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0078",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 38,
    "question": "In which city would you see the Last Supper, painted by Leonardo da Vinci?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brijing",
    "Wronganswer2": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer3": "London",
    "CORRECT": "Milan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0004",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 39,
    "question": "Machu Picchu is the most familiar symbol of the which empire?",
    "Wronganswer1": "France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer3": "India",
    "CORRECT": "Inca",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0035",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 40,
    "question": "What is this island prison?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Henderson",
    "Wronganswer2": "Kelvin Hall",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Colosseum",
    "CORRECT": "Alcatraz",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0062",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 41,
    "question": "Hall of Fame of what sport opened in Cooperstown, New York in 1939?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Basketball",
    "Wronganswer2": "Soccer",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tennis",
    "CORRECT": "Baseball",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0076",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 42,
    "question": "What is the middle part of Australia called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Greenway",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Mainland",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Centre",
    "CORRECT": "The Outback",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0018",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 43,
    "question": "Where is the Berlin Wall?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Egypt",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Germany",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0091",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 44,
    "question": "What type of natural landmark is Ipanema, located in Brazil?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lake",
    "Wronganswer2": "Wetland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Forest",
    "CORRECT": "Beach",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0096",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 45,
    "question": "Where is Michelangelo's David collected?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brisbane, Australia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Manchester, England",
    "Wronganswer3": "Paris, France",
    "CORRECT": "Florence, Italy",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0065",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 46,
    "question": "What did Emperor Shi Huandi command to be built for defence?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Kolner Dom",
    "Wronganswer2": "Arch of Triumph",
    "Wronganswer3": "Honolulu",
    "CORRECT": "Great Wall",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0095",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 47,
    "question": "Where the Archaeological Site of Troy?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer3": "Algeria",
    "CORRECT": "Turkey",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0040",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 48,
    "question": "What is this prehistoric cultural temple?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sentosa",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Cook",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ponte Vecchio",
    "CORRECT": "Stonehenge",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0093",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 49,
    "question": "Leaning Tower of Pisa is one of the most famous landmarks of which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Libya",
    "Wronganswer3": "Thailand",
    "CORRECT": "Italy",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0060",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 50,
    "question": "What is New Mexico's longest river?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Panama Canal",
    "Wronganswer2": "Suez Canal",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Nile",
    "CORRECT": "Rio Grande",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0025",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 51,
    "question": "Where is Mount Kilimanjaro?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Germany",
    "Wronganswer3": "Indonesia",
    "CORRECT": "Tanzania",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0084",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 52,
    "question": "'Birthplace of American freedom' best describes which landmark?",
    "Wronganswer1": "St. Peter's Basilica",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Wailing Wall",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Vatican",
    "CORRECT": "Independence Hall",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0088",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 53,
    "question": "Taj Mahal is found in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Scotland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Germany",
    "Wronganswer3": "Indonesia",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0099",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 54,
    "question": "Where is Bali located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Iran",
    "Wronganswer2": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ireland",
    "CORRECT": "Indonesia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0073",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 55,
    "question": "What 2200-mile bicycle race is held in France each year?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Wayfarer Race",
    "Wronganswer2": "French National Bicycle Race",
    "Wronganswer3": "Champagne National",
    "CORRECT": "Tour De France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0001",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 56,
    "question": "Which state does Yellowstone National Park not pass through?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Montana",
    "Wronganswer2": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer3": "Idaho",
    "CORRECT": "Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0048",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 57,
    "question": "What is this famous London structure?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Moscow White House",
    "Wronganswer2": "Buckingham Palace",
    "Wronganswer3": "Diaoyu Fortress",
    "CORRECT": "St. Paul's Cathedral",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0059",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 58,
    "question": "What is Japanese highest mountain?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Everest",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Olympus",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mount Kenya",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Fuji",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0012",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 59,
    "question": "Which one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World was built around 2500 BC?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Taj Mahal",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Wall of China",
    "Wronganswer3": "Brooklyn Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Great Pyramid of Giza",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0066",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 60,
    "question": "What color is the Golden Gate Bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Yellow",
    "Wronganswer2": "Black",
    "Wronganswer3": "White",
    "CORRECT": "Red",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0063",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 61,
    "question": "What famous landmark locates in Copenhagen harbor?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Colosseum",
    "Wronganswer2": "Giant Crab Statue",
    "Wronganswer3": "Stonehenge",
    "CORRECT": "Little Mermaid Statue",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0092",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 62,
    "question": "Which American city is the curvy Lombard Street and Fisherman's Wharf in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dallas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lynchburg",
    "Wronganswer3": "Los Angeles",
    "CORRECT": "San Francisco",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0051",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 63,
    "question": "What is this Berlin monument?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Tower Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tokyo Tower",
    "Wronganswer3": "Berlin Wall",
    "CORRECT": "Brandenburg Gate",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0100",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 64,
    "question": "Autobahns are mainly located in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Africa",
    "Wronganswer2": "United States",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ireland",
    "CORRECT": "Germany",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0069",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 65,
    "question": "What bridge is this?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Brooklyn Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bay Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Tower Bridge",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0021",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 66,
    "question": "Where is the Sahara Desert?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Asia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer3": "United States",
    "CORRECT": "Africa",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0036",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 67,
    "question": "What is this Westminster landmark?",
    "Wronganswer1": "St. Basil's Cathedral",
    "Wronganswer2": "Vorontsovsky Palace",
    "Wronganswer3": "Osaka Castle",
    "CORRECT": "Buckingham Palace",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0082",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 68,
    "question": "In which country is the Great Barrier Reef  located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0077",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 69,
    "question": "Where is the Leaning Tower of Pisa located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "India",
    "Wronganswer2": "France",
    "Wronganswer3": "Canada",
    "CORRECT": "Italy",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0005",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 70,
    "question": "Which president does not have his portrait carved in Mount Rushmore?",
    "Wronganswer1": "George Washington",
    "Wronganswer2": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "Wronganswer3": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "CORRECT": "Bill Clinton",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0097",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 71,
    "question": "What is the total length of the Great Wall of China?",
    "Wronganswer1": "500 miles",
    "Wronganswer2": "250 miles",
    "Wronganswer3": "50 miles",
    "CORRECT": "More than 4,000 miles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0017",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 72,
    "question": "Which bridge made with over 80,000 miles of steel wire locates in San Francisco?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Silver Gate Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Platinum Gate Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Balsa Wood Gate Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0013",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 73,
    "question": "Which famous bridge completed in 1937 was the brainchild of Joseph Strauss?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Los Angeles Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "London Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Rialto Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0090",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 74,
    "question": "Mount Everest is located in which continent?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South America",
    "Wronganswer2": "North America",
    "Wronganswer3": "Europe",
    "CORRECT": "Asia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0044",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 75,
    "question": "What is this Incan citadel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Great Wall of China",
    "Wronganswer2": "Easter Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Colosseum",
    "CORRECT": "Machu Picchu",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0024",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 76,
    "question": "Where is Stonehenge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Libya",
    "Wronganswer2": "United States",
    "Wronganswer3": "Botswana",
    "CORRECT": "Great Britain",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0061",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 77,
    "question": "What is a famous Egyptian statue with a lion's body and a human's head?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pharaoh",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mummy",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pyramid",
    "CORRECT": "Sphinx",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0074",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 78,
    "question": "What 1969 New York music festival featured The Who, Jimi Hendrix and Janis Joplin?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Altamont",
    "Wronganswer2": "Monterey Pop",
    "Wronganswer3": "Concert In Central Park",
    "CORRECT": "Woodstock",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0071",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 79,
    "question": "What Australian attraction is this?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Notre Dame",
    "Wronganswer2": "Buckingham Palace",
    "Wronganswer3": "St. Basil's Cathedral",
    "CORRECT": "Sydney Opera House",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0050",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 80,
    "question": "What is this Cambodian structure called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Taj Mahal",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bangalore Palace",
    "Wronganswer3": "Grand Kremlin Palace",
    "CORRECT": "Angkor Wat",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0029",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 81,
    "question": "What is this Presidential landmark?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Grand Canyon",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hoover Dam",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington Monument",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Rushmore",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0042",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 82,
    "question": "What is this Japanese landmark?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Eiffel Tower",
    "Wronganswer2": "Space Needle",
    "Wronganswer3": "Leaning Tower of Pisa",
    "CORRECT": "Tokyo Tower",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0064",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 83,
    "question": "What early U.S. patriot and inventor founded the school, which became the University of Pennsylvania?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Barack Obama",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bill Clinton",
    "Wronganswer3": "Abe Lincoln",
    "CORRECT": "Benjamin Franklin",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0043",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 84,
    "question": "What is this Indian mausoleum?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Angkor Wat",
    "Wronganswer2": "Notre Dame",
    "Wronganswer3": "St. Basil's Cathedral",
    "CORRECT": "Taj Mahal",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0003",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 85,
    "question": "Which is this waterfall?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Angel Falls",
    "Wronganswer2": "Iguazu Falls",
    "Wronganswer3": "Havasu Falls",
    "CORRECT": "Niagara Falls",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0039",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 86,
    "question": "What is this Russian attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Taj Mahal",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sydney Opera House",
    "Wronganswer3": "Buckingham Palace",
    "CORRECT": "St. Basil's Cathedral",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0033",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 87,
    "question": "Below what Kentucky town was an $11 billion gold mine?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bowling Green",
    "Wronganswer2": "Frankfort",
    "Wronganswer3": "Shelbyville",
    "CORRECT": "Fort Knox",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0041",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 88,
    "question": "What is this old Scottish fortress?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Buckingham Palace",
    "Wronganswer2": "Osaka Castle",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Tower of London",
    "CORRECT": "Edinburgh Castle",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0014",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 89,
    "question": "Which country created and donated the Statue of Liberty?",
    "Wronganswer1": "England",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer3": "Holland",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0027",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 90,
    "question": "What's the only one of the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World that keep standing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Colossus of Rhodes",
    "Wronganswer2": "Temple of Artemis",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "CORRECT": "Pyramids of Egypt",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0011",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 91,
    "question": "In which Italian city are buildings built on water in a lagoon?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer2": "Florence",
    "Wronganswer3": "Naples",
    "CORRECT": "Venice",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0046",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 92,
    "question": "What is this historic Japanese landmark?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Winter Palace",
    "Wronganswer2": "Kerak Castle",
    "Wronganswer3": "Red Fort",
    "CORRECT": "Osaka Castle",
    "pic": 1
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0072",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 93,
    "question": "Which landmark is consist of Superior, Huron, Michigan, Erie and Ontario?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Five Oceans",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Seven Seas",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Big Lakes",
    "CORRECT": "The Great Lakes",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0087",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 94,
    "question": "Why did the ancient Egyptians build the pyramids?",
    "Wronganswer1": "As A Competition",
    "Wronganswer2": "To Hold Sporting Events",
    "Wronganswer3": "For Fancy Gatherings",
    "CORRECT": "To Bury Royalty",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0026",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 95,
    "question": "Where are the Romans used to socializing and bathing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pantheon",
    "Wronganswer2": "Colosseum",
    "Wronganswer3": "Red Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Baths",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0195",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 1,
    "question": "Which one of the most famous beaches in the world is 4-km long in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Long Beach",
    "Wronganswer2": "Waikiki Beach",
    "Wronganswer3": "El Nido",
    "CORRECT": "Copacabana",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0182",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "What is held in the right hand of Lady Liberty in the Statue of Liberty?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Book",
    "Wronganswer2": "Flag",
    "Wronganswer3": "Money",
    "CORRECT": "Torch",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0186",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "What did the state of Kansas rename in honor of the heroic nurse Clara Barton?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Barton River",
    "Wronganswer2": "Barton Lake",
    "Wronganswer3": "Fort Barton",
    "CORRECT": "Barton County",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0075",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 4,
    "question": "The U.S dig a canal through what country from 1904 to 1914?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer2": "Nicaragua",
    "Wronganswer3": "Iceland",
    "CORRECT": "Panama",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0169",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "What type of collection can be found at the Greenwich Fan Museum, which is the only one of its kind?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Boats",
    "Wronganswer2": "Airplanes",
    "Wronganswer3": "Shells",
    "CORRECT": "Fans",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0178",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "What is Thomas Jefferson's home in Virginia called, which he designed himself?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Limoncello",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bordello",
    "Wronganswer3": "Portobello",
    "CORRECT": "Monticello",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0127",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 7,
    "question": "Which U.S. President is not depicted on Mount Rushmore?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "Wronganswer2": "George Washington",
    "Wronganswer3": "Theodore Roosevelt",
    "CORRECT": "Richard Nixon",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0197",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 8,
    "question": "Victor Hugo's 'The Hunchback of Notre Dame' is set in what country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chile",
    "Wronganswer2": "New Zealand",
    "Wronganswer3": "Japan",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0224",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 9,
    "question": "Where can you find The Terracotta Army?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer2": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer3": "Japan",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0130",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 10,
    "question": "Which of these best describes the Golden Gate Bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Links Two Modern Nations",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spectacular Collapse In 1940",
    "Wronganswer3": "Its Clock Dials Are 23 Feet Square",
    "CORRECT": "Recognized Symbol Of San Francisco",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0199",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 11,
    "question": "Where can the Neon Sign Graveyard, an extension of the Neon Museum be found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York",
    "Wronganswer2": "Washington",
    "Wronganswer3": "Annheim",
    "CORRECT": "Las Vegas",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0218",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 12,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Mausoleum of the First Qin Emperor?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Saudi Arabia",
    "Wronganswer2": "India",
    "Wronganswer3": "Denmark",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0105",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 13,
    "question": "You would visit the Wailing Wall at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer2": "Egypt",
    "Wronganswer3": "South Dakota",
    "CORRECT": "Old City Of Jerusalem",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0196",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 14,
    "question": "What 30-m tall statue is located at the peak of the 700-m Corcovado mountain in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Christ The Rescuer",
    "Wronganswer2": "Christ The Deliverer",
    "Wronganswer3": "Christ The Emancipator",
    "CORRECT": "Christ The Redeemer",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0015",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 15,
    "question": "In which city can the Liberty Bell be found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York City",
    "Wronganswer2": "Washington",
    "Wronganswer3": "Boston",
    "CORRECT": "Philadelphia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0141",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 16,
    "question": "Which best describes the Gateway Arch?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Remnant Of Lake Bonneville",
    "Wronganswer2": "Built In Celebration Of The French Revolution",
    "Wronganswer3": "Flows Into The North Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Stainless Steel Structure Rises 630 Feet High",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0175",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 17,
    "question": "What is Westminster Abbey?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Queen's Residence",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bus Station",
    "Wronganswer3": "Opera House",
    "CORRECT": "Gothic Church",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0118",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 18,
    "question": "Where can you find Mount Rainier?",
    "Wronganswer1": "California",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Britain",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York",
    "CORRECT": "Washington",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0133",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 19,
    "question": "Which exquisite palace was ordered to build by Louis XIV of France?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Buckingham Palace",
    "Wronganswer2": "Windsor Castle",
    "Wronganswer3": "St. James's Palace",
    "CORRECT": "Palace Of Versailles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0203",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 20,
    "question": "What material is the Little Mermaid statue made of?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Limestone",
    "Wronganswer2": "Gold",
    "Wronganswer3": "Brass",
    "CORRECT": "Copper",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0209",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 21,
    "question": "In which city is the Parthenon located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Washington, D.C.",
    "Wronganswer2": "Los Angeles, California",
    "Wronganswer3": "London, England",
    "CORRECT": "Athens, Greece",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0210",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "In which capital city was the Tower Bridge erected?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Amsterdam",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ottawa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Canberra",
    "CORRECT": "London",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0131",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 23,
    "question": "Which honeymoon destination is nicknamed 'City of Lights'?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cancun",
    "Wronganswer2": "Miami",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York",
    "CORRECT": "Paris",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0132",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 24,
    "question": "Which famous scientist created the theory of evolution during the visit to the Galapagos Islands?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Isaac Newton",
    "Wronganswer2": "Albert Einstein",
    "Wronganswer3": "Carl Linnaeus",
    "CORRECT": "Charles Darwin",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0201",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 25,
    "question": "The majority of the Amazon Jungle is contained within which country, with 60% of the rainforest?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Suriname",
    "Wronganswer2": "Guyana",
    "Wronganswer3": "Venezuela",
    "CORRECT": "Brazil",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0159",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 26,
    "question": "Where is the casino Caesars Palace located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Casper, Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer2": "Atlantic City, New Jersey",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington, DC",
    "CORRECT": "Las Vegas, Nevada",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0102",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 27,
    "question": "Alcatraz prison can be found in which of these states?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Oregon",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Texas",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0166",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 28,
    "question": "Where can you visit Everglades National Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Texas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Georgia",
    "Wronganswer3": "California",
    "CORRECT": "Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0206",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 29,
    "question": "On what continent is The Great Barrier Reef located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Asia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Antarctica",
    "Wronganswer3": "Europe",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0139",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "Which is the true description about the Guggenheim Museum?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Birthplace Of American Freedom",
    "Wronganswer2": "Adjacent To A Famous Catholic Sanctuary",
    "Wronganswer3": "Contains The Magnificent Dome Of Michelangelo",
    "CORRECT": "Designed By Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0160",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 31,
    "question": "Where is Pearl Harbor located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York City",
    "Wronganswer2": "Boston",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alaska",
    "CORRECT": "Hawaii",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0055",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 32,
    "question": "What is the top of the Empire State Building currently used for?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Air traffic monitoring",
    "Wronganswer2": "Nothing",
    "Wronganswer3": "Space signals",
    "CORRECT": "Broadcasting radio signals",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0192",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 33,
    "question": "What body of water separates England from the mainland of Europe?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bering Sea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pacific Ocean",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lake Michigan",
    "CORRECT": "English Channel",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0150",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 34,
    "question": "Where is the Extraterrestrial Highway, the site of several UFO sightings?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer2": "Utah",
    "Wronganswer3": "Vermont",
    "CORRECT": "Nevada",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0157",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "Where is the famous Leaning Tower found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hamburg",
    "Wronganswer2": "Venice",
    "Wronganswer3": "Naples",
    "CORRECT": "Pisa",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0129",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 36,
    "question": "Which of these is true about the Berlin Wall?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Controls The Colorado River",
    "Wronganswer2": "Original Home Of Mickey Mouse",
    "Wronganswer3": "Built Along The Rhine River",
    "CORRECT": "Construction Began In 1961",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0194",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "What archaeological site in Peru was voted one of the new seven wonders of the world in 2007?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Petra",
    "Wronganswer2": "Taj Mahal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Giza Necropolis",
    "CORRECT": "Machu Picchu",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0111",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 38,
    "question": "You would visit the Gateway Arch at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Washington, DC",
    "Wronganswer2": "Alberta",
    "Wronganswer3": "Juneau",
    "CORRECT": "St. Louis",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0183",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 39,
    "question": "What is a colossal statue of Jesus Christ at the summit of Mount Corcovado in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Christ The Reclaimer",
    "Wronganswer2": "Christ The Regainer",
    "Wronganswer3": "Christ The Restorer",
    "CORRECT": "Christ The Redeemer",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0113",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 40,
    "question": "You would visit the Empire State Building at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Dakota",
    "Wronganswer2": "Arizona",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russia",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0119",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 41,
    "question": "Where can you find Grand Teton National Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Florida",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rhode Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Hawaii",
    "CORRECT": "Wyoming",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0171",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 42,
    "question": "The White House is on which street?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bourbon Street",
    "Wronganswer2": "Broadway",
    "Wronganswer3": "Rodeo Drive",
    "CORRECT": "Pennsylvania Avenue",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0023",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 43,
    "question": "Where is the Aswam Dam?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Korea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Vietnam",
    "Wronganswer3": "Germany",
    "CORRECT": "Egypt",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0172",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 44,
    "question": "What state is Arlington National Cemetery in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hawaii",
    "Wronganswer2": "Alaska",
    "Wronganswer3": "South Dakota",
    "CORRECT": "Virginia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0115",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 45,
    "question": "Where can you find Plymouth Rock?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South America",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rochester, New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pearl Harbor",
    "CORRECT": "Massachusetts",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0212",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 46,
    "question": "In which American state is the Hoover Dam located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New Mexico",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Oregon",
    "CORRECT": "Nevada",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0219",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 47,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Hiroshima Peace Memorial?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer2": "Saudi Arabia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russian Federation",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0185",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 48,
    "question": "What is the world famous sign in California's Hollywood Hills?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Welcome",
    "Wronganswer2": "Show Time",
    "Wronganswer3": "Movieland",
    "CORRECT": "Hollywood",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0179",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 49,
    "question": "What is the royal residence located in Kensington Gardens called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Gloucester Castle",
    "Wronganswer2": "Kent House",
    "Wronganswer3": "Notre Dame",
    "CORRECT": "Kensington Palace",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0168",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 50,
    "question": "What was the tallest building of U.S. in the world from 1974 through 1998?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Empire State Building",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Chrysler Building",
    "Wronganswer3": "The John Hancock Center",
    "CORRECT": "The Sears Tower",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0161",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 51,
    "question": "Where is Greenwich Village located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New Mexico",
    "Wronganswer2": "South Dakota",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0173",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 52,
    "question": "What South American jungle is the largest tropical rainforest in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mamazon",
    "Wronganswer2": "Horizon",
    "Wronganswer3": "Verizon",
    "CORRECT": "Amazon",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0143",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 53,
    "question": "Which best describes Great Salt Lake?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Carved By Sculptor Gutzon Borglum",
    "Wronganswer2": "75,000 Gallons Of Water Each Second",
    "Wronganswer3": "Flows Though Nine Countries",
    "CORRECT": "Remnant Of Lake Bonneville",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0116",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 54,
    "question": "Where can you find Niagara Falls?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Houston",
    "Wronganswer3": "South America",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0122",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 55,
    "question": "Where can you find Cape Horn?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer2": "Eastmost Point Of Africa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Athens",
    "CORRECT": "Southernmost Point Of South America",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0149",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 56,
    "question": "Where is the fictional Dracula's castle?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Rome",
    "CORRECT": "Transylvania",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0167",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 57,
    "question": "What Wisconsin-born architect designed Taliesin and the Guggenheim Museum?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Maya Lin",
    "Wronganswer2": "Christopher Alexander",
    "Wronganswer3": "Daniel Burnham",
    "CORRECT": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0227",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 58,
    "question": "Chernobyl can be found in which locations?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer2": "Idaho",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington",
    "CORRECT": "Ukraine",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0189",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 59,
    "question": "What city is the historic French Quarter located in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York",
    "Wronganswer2": "Boston",
    "Wronganswer3": "Carson City",
    "CORRECT": "New Orleans",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0154",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 60,
    "question": "Where is the Palace of Versailles located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Iraq",
    "Wronganswer2": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer3": "Haiti",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0217",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 61,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Palace and Park of Versailles?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer2": "Portugal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Saudi Arabia",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0170",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 62,
    "question": "What structure did Shah Jahan build at Agra in the 17th century as a tomb for his wife?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Angkor Wat",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Blue Mosque",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tamerlane Mausoleum",
    "CORRECT": "The Taj Mahal",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0151",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 63,
    "question": "Where is the English Channel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pompeii, Italy",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington",
    "CORRECT": "Western Europe",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0147",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 64,
    "question": "Which is a 4,200-foot suspension bridge located in San Francisco, California?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Clifton Bridge",
    "Wronganswer2": "Verrazano Narrows Bridge",
    "Wronganswer3": "Golden Arch Bridge",
    "CORRECT": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0138",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 65,
    "question": "Which is the true description about the Nile River?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Famous Museum",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cathedral Commissioned By Ivan The Terrible",
    "Wronganswer3": "World Famous Casino",
    "CORRECT": "Flows Though Nine Countries",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0193",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 66,
    "question": "What Arkansas city is the origin of 47 natural hot springs?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hope",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mountain Home",
    "Wronganswer3": "Little Rock",
    "CORRECT": "Hot Springs",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0083",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 67,
    "question": "The Eiffel Tower uses 20,000 what?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Light bulbs",
    "Wronganswer2": "Steps",
    "Wronganswer3": "Cameras",
    "CORRECT": "Cables",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0156",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 68,
    "question": "Where is the Ho Chi Minh Trail located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Poland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Germany",
    "Wronganswer3": "United States Of America",
    "CORRECT": "Vietnam",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0164",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 69,
    "question": "Where did the Wright brothers first fly for 59 seconds?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer2": "Menlo Park",
    "Wronganswer3": "Boston",
    "CORRECT": "Kitty Hawk",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0146",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 70,
    "question": "Which is the true description about Alcatraz?",
    "Wronganswer1": "A Ruin Lying Atop The Acropolis Of Athens",
    "Wronganswer2": "Undersea Wonderland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Park Contains More Than 2,000 Natural Arches",
    "CORRECT": "Famous Prison Island",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0123",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 71,
    "question": "Where can you find Badlands National Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New York",
    "Wronganswer2": "Old City Of Jerusalem",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alberta",
    "CORRECT": "South Dakota",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0211",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 72,
    "question": "In which capital city can the Coliseum be found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Vienna",
    "Wronganswer2": "Berlin",
    "Wronganswer3": "Madrid",
    "CORRECT": "Rome",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0205",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 73,
    "question": "The Great Barrier Reef is located off the northeastern coast of what continent?",
    "Wronganswer1": "North America",
    "Wronganswer2": "Antarctica",
    "Wronganswer3": "Asia",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0207",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 74,
    "question": "In which U.S. city would the Metropolitan Museum of Art be found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Seattle",
    "Wronganswer2": "Philadelphia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Boston",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0221",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 75,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Chartres Cathedral?",
    "Wronganswer1": "India",
    "Wronganswer2": "Thailand",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pakistan",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0220",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 76,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Cologne Cathedral?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sri Lanka",
    "Wronganswer2": "Portugal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russian Federation",
    "CORRECT": "Germany",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0181",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 77,
    "question": "What is the famous museum in London which houses realistic wax figures called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Queen's Wax Museum",
    "Wronganswer2": "National Gallery",
    "Wronganswer3": "Wax R Us",
    "CORRECT": "Madame Tussauds",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0114",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 78,
    "question": "You would visit the Alamo at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Washington, DC",
    "Wronganswer2": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer3": "South America",
    "CORRECT": "San Antonio, Texas",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0174",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 79,
    "question": "What landmark once named Yerba Buena locates in the California city ?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Old Faithful",
    "Wronganswer2": "Grand Canyon",
    "Wronganswer3": "Giant Ball Of Twine",
    "CORRECT": "Golden Gate Bridge",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0109",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 80,
    "question": "You would visit the Lincoln Memorial at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "California",
    "Wronganswer2": "North Carolina And Tennessee",
    "Wronganswer3": "Casper, Wyoming",
    "CORRECT": "Washington, DC",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0225",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 81,
    "question": "Huangya Pass, a major tourist attraction of Tianjin, is a small section of what Chinese attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Great Tower Of China",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Bridge Of China",
    "Wronganswer3": "Great Pyramid Of China",
    "CORRECT": "Great Wall Of China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0162",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 82,
    "question": "Where is Gettysburg located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Massachusetts",
    "Wronganswer2": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer3": "Vatican City",
    "CORRECT": "Pennsylvania",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0163",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 83,
    "question": "Where do people go to ice skate in New York City?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Broadway",
    "Wronganswer2": "Yankee Stadium",
    "Wronganswer3": "Empire State Building",
    "CORRECT": "Rockefeller Center",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0177",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 84,
    "question": "What is the Rose Bowl?",
    "Wronganswer1": "A Rock Formation In Taos",
    "Wronganswer2": "An Extinct Volcano In Washington",
    "Wronganswer3": "A Valley In Kentucky",
    "CORRECT": "A Famous Football Stadium",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0104",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 85,
    "question": "You would visit Yankee Stadium at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "San Antonio, Texas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pearl Harbor",
    "Wronganswer3": "Africa",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0126",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 86,
    "question": "Which U.S. state has its highest point at Mt. Rainier, measured at 14,410 feet?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Utah",
    "Wronganswer2": "Minnesota",
    "Wronganswer3": "Massachusetts",
    "CORRECT": "Washington",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0140",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 87,
    "question": "Which is the true description about the Great Barrier Reef?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Otherwise Known As The Palace Of Westminster",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Youngest Of The Rocky Mountains",
    "Wronganswer3": "Battle Ground From U.S. Civil War",
    "CORRECT": "Undersea Wonderland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0184",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 88,
    "question": "What historic fortified complex serves as the official residence of the Russian president?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Federal Palace",
    "Wronganswer2": "White House",
    "Wronganswer3": "Buckingham Palace",
    "CORRECT": "Moscow Kremlin",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0145",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 89,
    "question": "Which best describes Arches National Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "843 Acres In The Center Of The City",
    "Wronganswer2": "Oldest Part Of The City Established 1718",
    "Wronganswer3": "50.7 Miles Long And 300 Feet Wide",
    "CORRECT": "The Park Contains More Than 2,000 Natural Arches",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0226",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 90,
    "question": "Gondoliers row boats through the canals of what Italian city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Milan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer3": "Naples",
    "CORRECT": "Venice",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0222",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 91,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Cathedral of Notre-Dame?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Israel",
    "Wronganswer2": "Malta",
    "Wronganswer3": "United Kingdom",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0153",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 92,
    "question": "Where is the Rose Bowl located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pierre, South Dakota",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sydney, Australia",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York, New York",
    "CORRECT": "Pasadena, California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0200",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 93,
    "question": "In what city is the National Palace, which is the official seat of the Mexican government located ?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Puebla",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tijuana",
    "Wronganswer3": "Chihuahua",
    "CORRECT": "Mexico City",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0134",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 94,
    "question": "Which European town hosts a Disneyland Hotel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Berlin",
    "Wronganswer2": "Madrid",
    "Wronganswer3": "London",
    "CORRECT": "Paris",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0108",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 95,
    "question": "You would visit the Nile River in which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Athens",
    "Wronganswer2": "Germany",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York City",
    "CORRECT": "Africa",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0137",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 96,
    "question": "Which is the true description about the Wailing Wall?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Stainless Steel Structure Rises 630 Feet High",
    "Wronganswer2": "Roughly The Size Of Rhode Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Monument Of Freedom",
    "CORRECT": "Only Wall Left Of King Herold's Temple",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0112",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 97,
    "question": "You would visit the Florida Keys at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Washington, DC",
    "Wronganswer2": "Northern California",
    "Wronganswer3": "Southern California",
    "CORRECT": "South Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0148",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 98,
    "question": "Where is the Yangtze River?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brazil",
    "Wronganswer2": "India",
    "Wronganswer3": "Japan",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0121",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 99,
    "question": "Where can you find Coney Island?",
    "Wronganswer1": "London",
    "Wronganswer2": "South Dakota",
    "Wronganswer3": "Maryland",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0228",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 100,
    "question": "What name is Las Vegas' Las Vegas Boulevard commonly known by?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Main Street",
    "Wronganswer2": "Route 66",
    "Wronganswer3": "Secret Lane",
    "CORRECT": "The Strip",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0198",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 101,
    "question": "Vatican City, where the Pope resides, is a city-state entirely enclosed by what country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "England",
    "Wronganswer2": "France",
    "Wronganswer3": "Turkey",
    "CORRECT": "Italy",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0110",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 102,
    "question": "You would visit The Great Wall at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pennsylvania",
    "Wronganswer2": "Nevada",
    "Wronganswer3": "Egypt",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0144",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 103,
    "question": "Which best describes Gettysburg?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Seat Of The Roman Catholic Church",
    "Wronganswer2": "Previously Called Shangri-La",
    "Wronganswer3": "50.7 Miles Long And 300 Feet Wide",
    "CORRECT": "Battle Ground From U.S. Civil War",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0135",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 104,
    "question": "Which candy company owns a theme park in Pennsylvania?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Nestle",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cadbury",
    "Wronganswer3": "Peter Pan",
    "CORRECT": "Hershey",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0124",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 105,
    "question": "The theme park 'Dollywood' was named after whom?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dolley Madison",
    "Wronganswer2": "Carol Channing",
    "Wronganswer3": "Barbie",
    "CORRECT": "Dolly Parton",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0187",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 106,
    "question": "What country gave the Statue of Liberty to America?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer2": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer3": "Japan",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0158",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 107,
    "question": "Where is the famed Central Park located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Athens, Greece",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cambridge, Massachusetts",
    "Wronganswer3": "Baghdad, Iraq",
    "CORRECT": "New York City",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0188",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 108,
    "question": "What ancient civilization built the great city of Machu Pichu in Peru?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Circa",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tapioca",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alpaca",
    "CORRECT": "Inca",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0223",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 109,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Archaeological Site of Olympia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pakistan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Turkmenistan",
    "CORRECT": "Greece",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0103",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 110,
    "question": "Yosemite National Park can be found in what U.S. state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ukraine",
    "Wronganswer2": "Alaska",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lake Superior",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0142",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 111,
    "question": "Which best describes the English Channel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Third Largest Ocean In The World",
    "Wronganswer2": "Carved By Sculptor Gutzon Borglum",
    "Wronganswer3": "Roof Shaped Like Sails Of A Boat",
    "CORRECT": "Has Underground Tunnel For Passage",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0136",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 112,
    "question": "Which is the true description about Yosemite National Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Magic Kingdom",
    "Wronganswer2": "Where The Mayflower Landed",
    "Wronganswer3": "Largest U.S. City",
    "CORRECT": "Roughly The Size Of Rhode Island",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0152",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 113,
    "question": "Where is the United Nations building located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chicago",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rome",
    "Wronganswer3": "Paris",
    "CORRECT": "New York City",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0216",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 114,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Peking Man Site at Zhoukoudian?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Peru",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russian Federation",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0107",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 115,
    "question": "You would visit the U.S. Capitol Building at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Utah",
    "Wronganswer2": "Philadelphia",
    "Wronganswer3": "London",
    "CORRECT": "Washington, DC",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0213",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 116,
    "question": "In what state is Niagara Falls located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Maine",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pennsylvania",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ohio",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0202",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 117,
    "question": "The Louvre is located where?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer2": "Germany",
    "Wronganswer3": "Switzerland",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0208",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 118,
    "question": "In which U.S. city is the Liberty Bell found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Fayetteville",
    "Wronganswer2": "Aberdeen",
    "Wronganswer3": "Topeka",
    "CORRECT": "Philadelphia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0191",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 119,
    "question": "What Chilean island in the southeastern Pacific Ocean is most famous for its enigmatic giant stone statues?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Christmas Island",
    "Wronganswer2": "Halloween Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Valentine Island",
    "CORRECT": "Easter Island",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0176",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 120,
    "question": "What is the world's highest uninterrupted waterfall, with a height of 979 meters and a plunge of 807 meters?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spirit Falls",
    "Wronganswer2": "Devil Falls",
    "Wronganswer3": "Cherub Falls",
    "CORRECT": "Angel Falls",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0128",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 121,
    "question": "Which of these is a U.S. Civil War battle site located in Pennsylvania?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Atlanta",
    "Wronganswer2": "Appomattox",
    "Wronganswer3": "Sumter",
    "CORRECT": "Gettysburg",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0214",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 122,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Temple and Cemetery of Confucius?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Korea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Argentina",
    "Wronganswer3": "New Zealand",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0106",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 123,
    "question": "You would visit the Vatican at which location?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Dakota",
    "Wronganswer2": "Nevada",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington, DC",
    "CORRECT": "Rome",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0117",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 124,
    "question": "Where can you find Mount Rushmore?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Southern United States",
    "Wronganswer2": "St. Louis",
    "Wronganswer3": "Divides Africa And Russia",
    "CORRECT": "South Dakota",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0215",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 125,
    "question": "Where is the World Heritage site, Sydney Opera House?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Morocco",
    "Wronganswer2": "Greece",
    "Wronganswer3": "Denmark",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0190",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 126,
    "question": "What city is Buckingham Palace located in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Edinburgh",
    "Wronganswer2": "Boston",
    "Wronganswer3": "Frankfurt",
    "CORRECT": "London",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0180",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 127,
    "question": "What is the island that the Statue of Liberty sits on called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Long Island",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ellis Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Jones Island",
    "CORRECT": "Liberty Island",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0165",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 128,
    "question": "Where can you visit the Golden Gate Bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chicago",
    "Wronganswer2": "Miami",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York City",
    "CORRECT": "San Francisco",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0125",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 129,
    "question": "American veterans from which war have a memorial dedicated to them in Washington, DC?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spanish American",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexican",
    "Wronganswer3": "Philippine American",
    "CORRECT": "Vietnam",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0155",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 130,
    "question": "Where is the Little Mermaid statue located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Nice, France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Stockholm, Sweden",
    "Wronganswer3": "Warsaw, Poland",
    "CORRECT": "Copenhagen, Denmark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0058",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 131,
    "question": "What is the name of the big sinkhole in the middle of the sea in Belize?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mariana Trench",
    "Wronganswer2": "Belize Blue",
    "Wronganswer3": "The Sinker",
    "CORRECT": "The Great Blue Hole",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0120",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 132,
    "question": "Where can you find Disney World?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Uniontown, Washington",
    "Wronganswer2": "Juneau, Alaska",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York, New York",
    "CORRECT": "Orlando, Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "LAN0204",
    "category": "Landmarks",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 133,
    "question": "The Hudson River Bridge was named after which famous American?",
    "Wronganswer1": "George Bush",
    "Wronganswer2": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bill Clinton",
    "CORRECT": "George Washington",
    "pic": 0
  }
]
